Health Myths You Should Stop Believing
You’ve probably heard health tips from friends or family…
But some are flat-out myths that could harm more than help.
Myth one: “You need to drink 8 glasses of water daily.”
The truth? Your body’s needs vary by activity, climate, and diet.
Listen to your thirst, not a fixed number.
Myth two: “Carbs make you fat.” Not true!
Whole grains, fruits, and legumes are healthy carbs
packed with fiber and energy.
It’s excess refined carbs and sugars that lead to weight gain.
Myth three: “Cracking your knuckles causes arthritis.” Relax!
Studies show no direct link.
At worst, you might just annoy people.
But it doesn’t damage your joints.
Myth four: “Detox juices cleanse your body.”
Your liver and kidneys are your real detox machines.
No expensive juice is required.
Stop letting health myths control your life.
Follow facts, not fads.
Share this with someone who still believes these myths!