Sleep Myths You Should Stop Believing
Think you know the truth about sleep?
Some “facts” are actually myths.
They might be ruining your rest.
Myth one: “You can catch up on sleep during weekends.”
Sadly, no. Extra sleep can’t undo chronic sleep deprivation.
Your body works best with a consistent routine.
Myth two: “Everyone needs 8 hours of sleep.”
Not true for all. Some feel refreshed with 7, others need 9.
Quality matters as much as quantity.
Myth three: “Alcohol helps you sleep better.”
Alcohol may knock you out, but it disrupts deep sleep.
You wake groggy the next morning.
Myth four: “If you wake up at night, you’re unhealthy.”
Waking briefly is normal—if you fall back asleep quickly.
Better sleep comes from facts, not myths.
Share this and help a friend rest easier!